<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2024 Manuel Alcaraz Zambrano <manuelalcarazzam@gmail.com>
  SPDX-License-Identifier: CC0-1.0
 -->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.chessament</id>
  <provides>
    <binary>chessament</binary>
  </provides>
  <name>Chessament</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">شطرنج</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Chessament</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Chessament</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Chessament</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Chessament</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Chessament</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Chessament</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Chessament</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Chessament</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">Chessament</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Chessament</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">Chessament</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Chessament</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">Chessament</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Chessament</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Chessament</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Chessament</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Chessament</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Chessament</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Chessament</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Chessament</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Chessament</name>
  <summary>Chess tournament manager</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">مدير بطولة شطرنج</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Gestor de torneigs d'escacs</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Gestor de torneigs d'escacs</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Schachturniermanager</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Gestor de torneos de ajedrez</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Xake txapelketa kudeatzailea</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Šakkiturnausten hallinta</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Gestionnaire de tournoi d'échecs</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Xestor de torneos de xadrez</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">מנהל תחרויות שחמט</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Gestore di tornei di scacchi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">ჭადრაკის ტურნირის მმართველი</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">체스 토너먼트 관리자</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">Šaha turnīru pārvaldnieks</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Beheerder van een schaaktoernooi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Zarządzanie turniejami szachowymi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Gerenciador de torneio de xadrez</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Upravljalnik šahovskih turnirjev</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Schackturneringshanterare</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Satranç turnuvası yöneticisi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Керування шаховим турніром</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">国际象棋赛事管理系统</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <developer id="kde.org">
    <name>The KDE Community</name>
    <url>https://kde.org</url>
  </developer>
  <description>
    <p>Chessament is a chess tournament manager. It currently supports individual Swiss-system tournaments.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">تطبيق شطرنج هو برنامج لإدارة بطولات الشطرنج. يدعم حاليًا بطولات فردية بنظام سويسري.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Chessament és un gestor de torneigs d'escacs. Actualment permet torneigs individuals segons el sistema suís.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Chessament és un gestor de torneigs d'escacs. Actualment permet torneigs individuals segons el sistema suís.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Chessament ist ein Schachturniermanager. Er unterstützt derzeit individuelle Turniere nach dem Schweizer System.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Chessament xake txapelketa kudeatzaile bat da. Gaur egun, sistema suitzarreko banakako txapelketak onartzen ditu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Chessament on šakkiturnausten hallinta. Toistaiseksi se tukee yksittäisiä sveitsiläistyylisiä turnauksia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Chessament est un gestionnaire de tournoi d'échecs. Il prend actuellement en charges les tournois individuels du système suisse.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Chessament é un xestor de torneos de xadrez. Actualmente permite torneos individuais mediante o sistema suízo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">Chessament הוא מנהל תחרויות שחמט. כרגע הוא תומך בתחרויות עצמאיות בשיטה השווייצרית.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Chessament è un gestore di tornei di scacchi. Attualmente supporta tornei individuali con sistema svizzero.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">Chessament ჭადრაკის ტურნამენტის მმართველია. მას ამჟამად ინდივიდუალური შვეიცარიული სისტემის ტურნამენტების მხარდაჭერა გააჩნია.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Chessament는 체스 토너먼트 관리자입니다. 개인 스위스식 토너먼트를 지원합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">„Chessament“ ir šaha turnīru pārvaldnieks. Šī programma šobrīd atbalsta dažāda veida Šveices sistēmas turnīrus.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Chessament is een beheerder van schaaktoernooien. Het ondersteunt op dit moment individuele toernooien volgens het Zwitserse systeem.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Chessament jest programem do zarządzania turniejami szachowymi. Obecnie obsługuje pojedyncze turnieje w systemie szwajcarskim.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Chessament é um gerenciador de torneios de xadrez. Atualmente, ele suporta torneios individuais no sistema suíço.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Chessament je upravitelj šahovskih turnirjev. Trenutno podpira posamezne turnirje po švicarskem sistemu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Chessament är en schackturneringshanterare. Den stöder för närvarande individuella schweizerturneringar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Chessament, bir satranç turnuvası yöneticisidir. Şu anda yalnızca İsviçre tarzı turnuvaları destekler.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Chessament — програма для керування шаховими турнірами. У поточній версії передбачено турніри за індивідуальною швейцарською системою.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">Chessament 是一个国际象棋赛事管理系统。目前支持举办个人瑞士制比赛。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/chessament/</url>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.chessament.desktop</launchable>
</component>
